A Guide to the Office of the Messrs. Rockefeller records, Business Interests, Series C FA312
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Companies
  - Companies - Delaware and Hudson Company, 1906-1931 (Box 28, Folder 243)
    Purchase of securities; participation in syndicate; small stock holdings. Correspondents include Bertram Cutler.
    62D2
  - Companies - Delaware, Lackawanna and Western Railway Company, 1902-1937 (Box 28, Folder 244)
    Investment; coal land interests; 1902 report on United Auto Workers activities. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Bertram Cutler.
    62D3
  - Companies - Delaware, Lackawanna and Western Railway Company - Delaware, Lackawanna and Western Coal Company, 1902-1932 (Box 28, Folder 245)
    Rockefeller interest in rebuilding Lackawanna Securities Company, 1927-1929. Holding company.
  - Companies - Delaware, Lackawanna and Western Railway Company - Lackawanna Securities, 1927-1929 (Box 28, Folder 246)
  - Companies - Denver and Rio Grande Railway, 1908-1924 (Box 29, Folder 247)
    Purchase of securities; syndicate operations. Bertram Cutler on Bondholders Protective Committee. Correspondents include Bertram Cutler.
    62D31
  - Companies - Denver and Rio Grande Railway - 1st Refunding Morgage 5% Bonds, 1916-1921 (Box 29, Folder 248)
  - Companies - Denver and Rio Grande Railway - 7% Adjustment Mortgage Bonds, 1913-1916 (Box 29, Folder 249)
  - Companies - Denver and Rio Grande Railway - 6% Convertible Gold Notes, 1908 (Box 29, Folder 250)
  - Companies - Denver and Rio Grande Railway - 5% Gold Bond Syndicate, 1908-1912 (Box 29, Folder 251)
  - Companies - Interborough Rapid Transit, 1912-1939 (Box 29, Folder 252)
    Bertram Cutler on Board of Directors as Rockefeller representative; Bertram Cutler's reports, 1925-1932. 1913, John D. Rockefeller purchase of over $4,000,000 of Interborough Rapid Transit Bonds through Morgan syndicate. Correspondents include Bertram Cutler, John D. Rockefeller.
    62In1
    See also Mark M. Jones Papers.
  - Companies - Manhattan Railway Company, 1903-1937 (Box 29, Folder 253)
    John D. Rockefeller invested over $10,000,000; control of Board, financial operations, re-organization of Interborough. Manhattan leased property to Interborough. Struggle between Manhattan and Interborough Rapid Transit; Rockefellers sell interest, retained bonds. Bertram Cutler on Protective Committee. Connections with Goulds, 1903-1913. Correspondents include Starr J. Murphy, Bertram Cutler, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., George Gould.
    62M1
  - Companies - Manhattan Railway Company, 1903-1937 (Box 29, Folder 0253A)
  - Companies - Manhattan Railway Company - 2nd Mortgage, 1932-1936 (Box 29, Folder 254)
    Payments of interest on 2nd mortgage stopped by company; Bertram Cutler then joined Committee. Securities and Exchange Commission questionnaire.
  - Companies - Manhattan Railway Company - Stockholders Protective Committee, 1922 (Box 30, Folder 255)
    Organization of Committee; deposit of stock.
  - Companies - Missouri, Kansas and Texas Railway, 1903-1922 (Box 30, Folder 256)
    Rockefeller investment; reorganization. Correspondents include Bertram Cutler.
    62M5
  - Companies - Missouri, Kansas and Texas Railway - Bondholders Committee, 1916-1923 (Box 30, Folder 257)
  - Companies - Missouri, Kansas and Texas Railway - 1st 5% Gold Bonds, 1903 (Box 30, Folder 258)
  - Companies - Missouri, Kansas and Texas Railway - Refunding 4% Bonds, 1909 (Box 30, Folder 259)
  - Companies - Missouri Pacific Railway, 1915-1934 (Box 30, Folder 260)
    Rockefeller investment; studies of financial structure of 1915 reorganization. Correspondents include Bertram Cutler.
    62M6
  - Companies - New York Central Lines, 1921-1951 (Box 30, Folder 261)
    Bertram Cutler on Board of Directors; stock purchase; relations between New York Central Lines and Pocantico estate. Correspondents include Bertram Cutler, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., F. DeLap.
    62N4
  - Companies - New York Central Lines - Elimination of Grade Crossings at Pocantico, 1924-1928 (Box 30, Folder 262)
  - Companies - New York Central Lines - Philadelphia and Reading Coal and Iron Corporation, 1924-1935 (Box 30, Folder 263)
    Securities.
  - Companies - New York Central Lines - Marymount Fence, 1941-1944 (Box 30, Folder 264)
  - Companies - New York Central - Relocation of Putnam Division - John D. Rockefeller-John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Correspondence (Box 30, Folder 265)
    Personal interest in changes, relocation. Clippings; opposition to change.
  - Companies - New York Central - Relocation of Putnam Division - Tarrytown and North Tarrytown Approval, 1929 (Box 30, Folder 266)
    Charles O. Heydt's campaign work.
  - Companies - New York Central - Relocation of Putnam Division - Bid Settlement, 1931-1932 (Box 30, Folder 267)
    Approval of charges; payment of $778,000.
  - Companies - New York Central - Relocation of Putnam Division, 1916-1936 (Box 30, Folder 268)
    Removal of Pocantico Hills station discussed, 1916-1929; John D. Rockefeller, Jr. helped finance some of changes. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Charles O. Heydt.
  - Companies - New York Central - Relocation of Tracks - Eastview - Clippings, 1931-1932 (Box 30, Folder 269)
  - Companies - New York Central - Right of Way, 1930-1938 (Box 31, Folder 270)
    Clearing claims to New York Central right-of-way deed to John D. Rockefeller, Jr. in exchange for new route of Putnam branch. Exchange of lands. Correspondents include Charles O. Heydt, Thomas M. Debevoise, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  - Companies - New York Central - Right of Way, 1939-1942 (Box 31, Folder 271)
  - Companies - New York Central - Right of Way, 1943-1947 (Box 31, Folder 272)
  - Companies - New York Central - Right of Way - Cable Easement, 1935-1937 (Box 31, Folder 273)
  - Companies - New York Central - Right of Way - Gift to Board of Water Commissioners, 1941-1950 (Box 31, Folder 274)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. gave section of old Putnam division right-of-way to Village of Tarrytown in 1942. Additional land in same area given in 1945.
  - Companies - New York Central - Right of Way - Railroad Crossing, Rockwood Property, 1941-1957 (Box 31, Folder 275)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. maintained permission to cross New York Central tracks and to build a footbridge across tracks; Laurance S. Rockefeller renewed permission in 1957.
  - Companies - New York Central and Hudson River Railroad, 1902-1921 (Box 32, Folder 276)
    Purchase of securities; representation of Board. Correspondents include Bertram Cutler, John D. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  - Companies - New York Central and Hudson River Railroad - 4 1/2% Gold Bonds, 1915 (Box 32, Folder 277)
  - Companies - New York Central and Hudson River Railroad - Syndicates, 1914 (Box 32, Folder 278)
  - Companies - New York Central and Hudson River Railroad - New York Central 4% Debenture Bonds, 1904 (Box 32, Folder 279)
  - Companies - New York Central - Transmission Lines, 1939 (Box 32, Folder 280)
    Establishing restrictions on height of power transmission lines on new railroad right of way; arrangements with Westchester Lighting Company. Use of gravel pit. Correspondents include Charles O. Heydt, Thomas M. Debevoise, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
    62N41
  - Companies - New York Central - Transmission Lines, 1941-1942 (Box 32, Folder 281)
  - Companies - New York Central - Transmission Lines, 1942-1943 (Box 32, Folder 282)
  - Companies - New York Central - Transmission Lines, 1943-1960 (Box 32, Folder 283)
  - Companies - New York Central - Transmission Lines - Agreement with Westchester Lighting Company, 1942 (Box 32, Folder 284)
  - Companies - St. Louis and San Francisco Railroad Company, 1906-1917 (Box 32, Folder 285)
    Purchase of securities; bankruptcy. Correspondents include H. E. Cooper, Frederick T. Gates.
    62S1
  - Companies - St. Louis and San Francisco Railroad Company - Mexico Division, 1911 (Box 32, Folder 286)
    Syndicate; first mortgage bonds.
  - Companies - Southern Railway Equipments, 1908-1918 (Box 33, Folder 287)
    Purchase of equipment certificates; collection of interest; sale of certificates. Correspondents include Bertram Cutler, H. E. Cooper.
    62S71A
  - Companies - Western Maryland Railroad, 1912-1915 (Box 33, Folder 288)
    Frederick T. Gates resigns from Board; negotiations for sale of stock. 1922 and 1926 strikes. Management problems. Sale of Baltimore and Ohio, 1927; arrangements between Consolidation Coal, Western Maryland Railroad and Baltimore and Ohio.
    62W3
  - Companies - Western Maryland Railroad, 1915-1916 (Box 33, Folder 289)
  - Companies - Western Maryland Railroad, 1917-1923 (Box 33, Folder 290)
  - Companies - Western Maryland Railroad - 1925 Strike, 1925-1927 (Box 33, Folder 291)
    Raymond B. Fosdick's Industrial Relations Council investigates and modifies conditions before strike; local management insists on its own ways. Appeals from citizens; John D. Rockefeller, Jr. disclaims responsibility. Senatorial attach on John D. Rockefeller, Jr. over railroad's strike policies. Correspondents include Raymond B. Fosdick, M. C. Byers, Ivy Lee.
  - Companies - Western Maryland Railroad - Sale of Wheeling-Lake Erie Stock, 1927 (Box 33, Folder 292)
  - Companies - Western Maryland Railroad - Strike of Engineers - Clippings, 1925 (Box 33, Folder 293)
  - Companies - Western Maryland Railroad - Federal Council Report, 1926 (Box 33, Folder 294)
  - Companies - Davis Coal and Coke Company, 1912-1939 (Box 34, Folder 295)
    Frederick T. Gates' investigation of 1912 mine disaster; introduction of Industrial Relations idea; Calloway's objection to "do gooders" in his business. H. P. Fish on Board; wartime operations; depression problems. Gift of stock to Rockefeller Institute. Impact of National Industrial Recovery Act on industry. Correspondents include Frederick T. Gates, Bertram Cutler, Thomas M. Debevoise, A. Calloway, H. P. Fish.
    62W3A
  - Companies - Davis Coal and Coke Company, 1928-1934 (Box 34, Folder 296)
  - Companies - Davis Coal and Coke Company, 1935-1952 (Box 34, Folder 297)
  - Companies - Davis Coal and Coke Company - Monongalia Lands, 1914-1927 (Box 34, Folder 298)
    Owned by Davis Coal and Coke Company; management of lands; efforts to sell.
  - Companies - Davis Coal and Coke Company - A. Calloway - Salary, 1920 (Box 34, Folder 299)
    Increase in salary for wartime service.
  - Companies - Davis Coal and Coke Company - Stockholders' Protectors Corporation, 1932-1934 (Box 34, Folder 300)
    Outsiders' attempt to force dividends unsuccessful.
  - Companies - Davis Coal and Coke Company - Industrial Representation Plan, 1916-1918 (Box 34, Folder 301)
    Extra copies of plan.
  - Companies - Consolidation Coal Company, 1915-1923 (Box 34, Folder 302)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s interest in company plans; Raymond B. Fosdick's role. Rockefellers assume responsibility for management in 1928 after Senate hearings; Anderson's new policies. Comments on coal industry; financial problems, 1930; receivership. 1932 strike; effects of National Recovery Act, 1937 Guffey Act. Nelson A. Rockefeller represented John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Bertram Cutler, Thomas M. Debevoise, Raymond B. Fosdick, Nelson A. Rockefeller, G. J. Anderson.
    62W3B
  - Companies - Consolidation Coal Company, 1925-1932 (Box 34, Folder 303)
  - Companies - Consolidation Coal Company, 1932-1946 (Box 35, Folder 304)
  - Companies - Consolidation Coal Company - J. H. Wheelwright, 1915-1920 (Box 35, Folder 305)
    President of company. 1916 labor problems.
  - Companies - Consolidation Coal Company - Coastwise Transportation, 1915-1920 (Box 35, Folder 306)
    Subsidiary bought for ships; sold after war at a profit.
  - Companies - Consolidation Coal Company - Stock Purchasing Plan, 1920 (Box 35, Folder 307)
    For officers of company; plan not carried out.
  - Companies - Consolidation Coal Company - Dividend, 1917-1926 (Box 35, Folder 308)
    Rockefeller attitude toward dividend payments.
  - Companies - Consolidation Coal Company - Preferred Stock Issue, 1924 (Box 35, Folder 310)
  - Companies - Consolidation Coal Company - Labor Policy, 1934 (Box 35, Folder 309)
    Company union statement in 1934 when United Mine Workers was reorganized.
  - Companies - Consolidation Coal Company - Coal Strike Situation, 1922 (Box 35, Folder 311)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. and Raymond B. Fosdick oppose company's policy re labor and strike; John D. Rockefeller, Jr. speaks out for strikers.
  - Companies - Consolidation Coal Company - 1925 Strike (Box 35, Folder 312)
    Newspaper clippings re strike threat. Correspondence among C. W. Watson, John L. Lewis and John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Evictions from company houses.
  - Companies - Consolidation Coal Company - Senator Watson Correspondence, 1915-1940 (Box 35, Folder 313)
    Contacts with Frederick T. Gates and John D. Rockefeller, Jr.; John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s inspection tour. Friendly sentiments. C. W. Watson's retirement, death. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Frederick T. Gates, C. W. Watson.
  - Companies - Consolidation Coal Company - Report - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) (Box 35, Folder 314)
  - Companies - Consolidation Coal Company - John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Inspection Tour, 1915-1916 (Box 36, Folder 315)
  - Companies - Consolidation Coal Company - John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Inspection Tour - Elkhorn Material - Trip June 1916 (Box 36, Folder 316)
    1915 financial plan; analysis of company; John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s 1915-1916 inspection tour. Local newspaper clippings re tour. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., C. R. Gray.
  - Companies - Consolidation Coal Company - John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Inspection Tour - Elkhorn Material - Clipping re Trip December 1915, 1916 (Box 36, Folder 317)
  - Companies - Consolidation Coal Company - John D. Rockefeller's Financial Interest, 1915-1921 (Box 36, Folder 318)
    Original bond investment; conversion of bonds to stocks; additions through open market purchases. Control of company. Transfer of stock to John D. Rockefeller, Jr. and Rockefeller Foundation. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Bertram Cutler, Frederick T. Gates.
  - Companies - Consolidation Coal Company - John D. Rockefeller's Financial Interest - 1st Mortgage 5% Bonds, 1917 (Box 36, Folder 319)
  - Companies - Consolidation Coal Company - Purchase of 5% Gold Notes, 1929-1937 (Box 36, Folder 320)
    Purchase of Gold Notes issued in 1931.
  - Companies - Consolidation Coal Company - Reorganization, 1932-1941 (Box 36, Folder 321)
    Negotiations of bondholders committees arranging receivership; court approval of plan; control of receivers committee. Correspondents include Thomas M. Debevoise, Bertram Cutler, B. P. Turnbull.
  - Companies - Consolidation Coal Company - Reorganization - Charter and By-Laws of Reorganization Campaign Receivership, 1932-1935 (Box 36, Folder 322)
  - Companies - Consolidation Coal Company - Reorganization - Receivership, 1932-1935 (Box 36, Folder 323)
    Membership of committee; operations of committee.
  - Companies - Consolidation Coal Company - Western Maryland Railroad Suit, 1930-1931 (Box 36, Folder 324)
    Suit re 1915 agreement on coal shipments over Western Maryland Railroad; Railroad claimed Consolidation Coal Company failed to fulfill contract. Settled out of court. Correspondents include Thomas M. Debevoise.
  - Companies - Consolidation Coal Company - Western Maryland Railroad Suit - Letters Used in Suit, 1914-1919 (Box 36, Folder 325)
  - Companies - Consolidation Coal Company - Western Maryland Railroad Suit - Frederick T. Gates Memoranda, 1915-1919 (Box 36, Folder 326)
    Summary of negotiations leading to purchase of Consolidation Coal.
  - Companies - Consolidation Coal Company - Western Maryland Railroad Suit - C. R. Gray, 1914-1919 (Box 36, Folder 327)
    Management of Consolidated Coal Company; Gray represented Rockefeller interest.
  - Companies - Consolidation Coal Company - Senate Inquiry, 1928 (Box 37, Folder 328)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. appeared before Committee as investor; J. L. Lewis had accused him of conspiracy to wreck union. Transcript of John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s testimony. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., G. J. Anderson, Thomas M. Debevoise.
  - Companies - Consolidation Coal Company - Senate Inquiry - Clippings, 1928 (Box 37, Folder 329)
  - Companies - Consolidation Coal Company - Relief Fund, 1931-1943 (Box 37, Folder 330)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s Advisory Committee contributed anonymously through company toward relief of unemployed workers: $5,000, 1927-1932. Description of needs. Return of $1,000 in 1933-1935. Correspondents include Raymond B. Fosdick, Robert W. Gumbel.
  - Companies - Consolidation Coal Company - 5% Notes - 1940 Transaction, 1938-1941 (Box 37, Folder 331)
    Refinancing part of debt structure; Rockefeller interest restricted to funds' ownership of company securities. Correspondents include Thomas M. Debevoise, B. P. Turnbull.
  - Companies - Pittsburgh Consolidated Coal Company, 1945-1952 (Box 37, Folder 332)
    By-laws; Turnbull a director. Miscellaneous correspondence. Correspondents include Thomas M. Debevoise.
    62W3B1
  - Companies - Pittsburgh Consolidated Coal Company - Reports to Securities Exchange Commission, 1945-1947 (Box 37, Folder 333)
    Turnbull owned 100 shares as a director.
  - Companies - Merchants Coal Company, 1915-1916 (Box 37, Folder 334)
    Early attempts to interest Rockefellers in purchase of company failed. 1917 purchase. Correspondents include C. W. Watson, Frederick T. Gates, E. H. Marston.
    62W3C
  - Companies - Western Pacific Railroad, 1905-1930 (Box 38, Folder 335)
    Frederick T. Gates memoranda on Gould railroad financing and manipulating. Rockefeller investment; sale of securities. Correspondents include Frederick T. Gates, Bertram Cutler, H. E. Cooper.
    62W4
  - Companies - Western Pacific Railroad - Reorganization, 1915-1927 (Box 38, Folder 336)
    Road's bankruptcy; reorganization. Rockefeller interests. Re dividends. Correspondents include Bertram Cutler, Starr J. Murphy.
  - Companies - Western Pacific Railroad - 1st Mortgage Bonds, 1915-1916 (Box 38, Folder 337)
    Investigation of railroad property by C. R. Gray, 1915; his report. Rockefeller interest and investment in railroad bonds, totalling $7,000,000. Correspondents include Bertram Cutler, C. R. Gray.
    62W41
  - Companies - Wheeling and Lake Erie Railroad, 1908-1927 (Box 38, Folder 338)
    Gould's proposition; Frederick T. Gates' condemnation of Gould's methods. Statement on profit and risk. rockefeller control after 1917; unloading of stock after 1919. Request to oil company that shipments be shifted to Wheeling; gift of Wheeling stock to John D. Rockefeller, Jr. in 1921. Was to connect with Western Maryland Railroad; bought out by New York Central, 1927. Correspondents include Frederick T. Gates, H. E. Cooper, Bertram Cutler, John D. Rockefeller.
    62W5
  - Companies - Wheeling and Lake Erie Railroad - Reorganization, 1917 (Box 38, Folder 339)
    Purchase by Rockefellers.
  - Companies - Wheeling and Lake Erie Railroad - Compensation for Mr. Duncan, 1927 (Box 38, Folder 340)
  - Companies - Offerings of Stocks and Bonds, 1905-1944 (Box 38, Folder 341)
    Offers of investment advice; material on the 1930 Chicago "bankruptcy" incident. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. investment in Missouri Soldier Bonus Bonds. Reports on miscellaneous stocks and bonds purchases. Correspondents include E. V. Cary, H. E. Cooper, Bertram Cutler.
    62.1D
  - Companies - Airborne Instruments Laboratory, 1950-1951 (Box 38, Folder 342)
    Purchase of company stock.
    62.2A
    DR material removed to Folder 342A.
  - Companies - Airborne Instruments Laboratory, 1950-1951 (Box 38, Folder 0342A)
  - Companies - American Cyanamid Company, 1944-1955 (Box 38, Folder 343)
    Thomas M. Debevoise's trip to South Carolina laboratories. Testing of cancer drugs, aureomycin, polio cures. K. C. Towe's 1955 address to New York Society of Security Analysts. Correspondents include Thomas M. Debevoise, W. B. Bell.
    62.2A2
  - Companies - American Telephone and Telegraph, 1930-1951 (Box 38, Folder 344)
    List of stocks owned by various Rockefellers; nothing of importance re AT&T. Correspondents include Walter S. Giffordi, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Bertram Cutler.
    62.2A4
  - Companies - American Telephone and Telegraph - 7-Year 6% Bond Syndicate, 1918 (Box 38, Folder 345)
    John D. Rockefeller participation up to $500,000, ended taking $150,000 worth, which he sold.
  - Companies - American Tobacco Company, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 346)
    Rockefeller objections to large incentive bonuses paid to company officials; study of American Tobacco policy; G. W. Hill defends policies. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller 3rd.
    62.2A42
  - Companies - Bethlehem Steel Company, 1948-1953 (Box 38, Folder 347)
    Information re company policies of pricing and contributing; early material missing. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
    62.2B
  - Companies - Beryllium Corporation, 1932-1948 (Box 39, Folder 348)
    John D. Rockefeller 3rd investment; no control by Rockefellers; no indication re return on investment. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller 3rd, B. P. Turnbull.
    62.2B1
  - Companies - Elk River Timber Company, 1946-1947 (Box 39, Folder 349)
    Laurance S. Rockefeller lent friend $200,000 for timber investment, though uninterested in long-range timber investment. Withdrew; loan repaid within year. Correspondents include Laurance S. Rockefeller, H. B. Marston.
    62.2E
  - Companies - General Motors Company, 1918-1960 (Box 39, Folder 350)
    John D. Rockefeller's investment; gift of stock to Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial Fund. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. investment. Correspondents include Bertram Cutler, John D. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
    62.2G
  - Companies - Compania Anonima Minera Gran Sabana, 1946-1949 (Box 39, Folder 351)
    Laurance S. Rockefeller and Rockefeller Brothers, Inc. investment in diamond prospecting syndicate: $50,000; no diamonds found, syndicate dissolved. Correspondents include Laurance S. Rockefeller.
    62.2G1
  - Companies - Hooker Electrochemical Company, 1938-1956 (Box 39, Folder 352)
    Equitable report on company, loan of large sum to it. John D. Rockefeller 3rd correspondence with Harry and Albert Hooker, related to his wife. John D. Rockefeller declines directorship; splitting of stock; disposition of Blanchette Hooker Rockefeller's stock holdings. Correspondents include Albert and Harry Hooker, John D. Rockefeller 3rd, B. P. Turnbull, Bertram Cutler.
    62.2H5
  - Companies - Hooker Electrochemical Company - Blanchette Hooker Rockefeller Stock, 1940-1949 (Box 39, Folder 353)
    Blanchette Hooker Rockefeller owned about 7 percent of outstanding stock; her sales and transfer of stock.
  - Companies - International Nickel Company of Canada, 1947-1959 (Box 40, Folder 354)
    Laurance S. Rockefeller a member of Board of Directors. Correspondents include Laurance S. Rockefeller.
    62.2I
  - Companies - Industrial Credit and Investment Corporation of India, 1952-1964 (Box 40, Folder 355)
    Investment by brothers; investigations of proposed company; cooperation with the United States Government and other United States companies. Stock gift to Rockefeller Brothers Fund. Company operated as development bank lending money to Indian industries. Correspondents include David Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller 3rd, John E. Lockwood, R. H. Mansfield.
    62.2I2
  - Companies - Industrial Credit and Investment Corporation of India, 1954-1961 (Box 40, Folder 356)